

Wildflowerinabox@gmail.com | 925-997-8067 | Orinda, United States 94563

Summary

Computer programming student pursuing an internship opportunity to gain hands-on experience. Outgoing and friendly with strong motivation for success. I recently graduated from a bootcamp program at UC Berkeley which taught me how to adapt quickly in a fast paced course.

Education and Training

UC Berkley Extension | Berkeley, CA **Computer Science** in Full Stack Development 12/2021

Skills

In my coding class I learned a multitude of skills including: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Heroku, Git, Database Theory, MVC frameworks and architecture (React), Object-Oriented Programming, and Pair Programming.

GitHub, Portfolio, LinkedIn

- https://github.com/Alix1713
- https://alix1713.github.io/Alix/
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/alix1713/

Experience

Sloat Garden Centers | Pleasant Hill, CA

Management Assistant

01/2018 - 10/2021

Sloat garden center | Danville, CA **Manager** 02/2015 - 01/2018

Sloat garden center | Mill Valley, CA **Assistant Store Manager** 02/2014 - 02/2015

Sloat garden center | Danville, CA **Buyer** 03/2012 - 02/2014

- Managed new hire trainings and onboarding to educated employees on company policies and procedures.
- Collaborated with staff to maximize customer satisfaction, streamline procedures and improve bottom-line profitability.
- Drove financial performance of assigned areas by verifying achieved sales and profit goals and implementing plans to correct deficiencies.
- Delivered level of service to customers in effort to build upon relationships for future clients.
- Set schedules and delegated assignments based on team strengths to optimize floor coverage and service levels.
- Documented purchasing activities, inventory reports and department records.
- Analyzed sales trends to maximize sales potential.